(Sheldon:)Boy, do I have to urinate.
(Leonard:)If only there were a solution
to that.
(Sheldon:)Seriously. I feel like I've got
a fish tank in my pelvis.
(Leonard:)So go to the bathroom.
(Sheldon:)I can't.
(Leonard:)Why not?
(Sheldon:)Because I'm trying to decide
between getting an Xbox One or a PS4.
Oh, "pee." Why'd I say that?
(Leonard:)Forgive me for asking
a stupid question,
(Leonard:)but why are you being stupid?
(Sheldon:)I'm not being stupid.
(Sheldon:)I'm employing the work
of Dutch researcher, Mirjam Tuk,
(Sheldon:)who found that people with full
bladders make better decisions.
(Leonard:)Why did I pee before I decided
to move in here?
'Hi!
-Hey. How'd the audition go?
(Penny:)I killed it. I was even able
to cry real tears right on the spot.
(Leonard:)-That's great.
-I know.
(Penny:)Next time I get pulled over
for a speeding ticket,
(Penny:)here come the waterworks.
Here come the waterworks!
(Leonard:)-Aren't you gonna ask?
-What is this, my first day?
I (THEME SONG PLAYS)